A Guide to the Board of Visitors of the University of Virginia Committee Records, 1980-1986
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
The Board of Visitors of the University of Virginia Committee Records 1980-1986
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-1/1/3.861
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions may apply to specific student records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.).
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library on 1986 Aug 6.
Contents List
- Audit Committee (2 folders) 1980-1981 (Box 1)
- Audit Committee 1982 (Box 1)
- Report on Audit: University of Virginia - Fiscal Year 1984/1985 1985 (Box 1)
- Special Review of Federal Circular A-110 Compliance-Fiscal Year 1982/1983 1984 (Box 1)
- Report on Audit: UVa/Federal Circular A-110 Compliance - Fiscal Year 1983/1984 1985 (Box 1)
- Report on Audit: UVa/Federal Circular A-110 Compliance - Fiscal Year 1984/1985 1986 (Box 1)
- Report on Audit: UVa/Federally Insured Loan Fund of the Law School Foundation-Fiscal Years 1981/1982 - 1982/1983 1984 (Box 1)
- Report on Audit: UVa/Federally Insured Loan Fund of the Law School Foundation-Fiscal Years 1983/1984 - 1984/1985 1986 (Box 1)
- Report on Audit: UVa/National Direct Student Loan Program, College Work Study Program, Supplemental Educational Opportunity Grants Program, and Pell Grant Program-Fiscal Years 1981/1982 - 1982/1983 1984 (Box 1)
- Report on Audit: UVa/Student Financial Assistance Programs - Fiscal Years 1983/1984-1984/1985 1986 (Box 1)
- Report on Audit: UVa/Student Housing System - Fiscal Year 1984/1985 1986 (Box 1)
- Report on Audit: UVa/Upward Bound Program - Fiscal Years 1981/1982 -1982/1983 1984 (Box 1)
- Report on Audit: UVa/Upward Bound Program - Fiscal Years 1983/1984 -1984/1985 1986 (Box 1)
- Report on Audit: UVa Hospital and Blue Ridge Hospital - Fiscal Year 1982/1983 1983 (Box 1)
- Report on Audit: UVa Hospitals - Fiscal Years 1983/1984 - 1984/1985 1985 (Box 1)
- Report on Audit: UVa - Clinch Valley College/Dormitory Revenue Bonds Series A and B Project Funds [CH-VA-SS(D)] - Fiscal Years 1981-1982 - 1982/1983 1984 (Box 2)
- Report on Audit: UVa-CVC/Dormitory Revenue Bonds Series A and B Project Funds - Fiscal Years 1983/1984-1984/1985 1986 (Box 2)
- Report on Audit: UVa-CVC/Faculty Housing Project-Fiscal Years 1981/1982 - 1982/1983 1984 (Box 2)
- Report on Audit: UVa-CVC/Faculty Housing Project Funds-Fiscal Years 1983/1984-1984/1985 1986 (Box 2)
- Report on Audit: UVa-CVC/Student Financial Assistance Programs - Fiscal Year 1984/1985 1986 (Box 2)
- Report on Audit: UVa/CVC/Upward Bound Program-Fiscal Years 1981/1982-1982/1983 1984 (Box 2)
- Report on Audit: UVa/CVC/Upward Bound Program-Fiscal Years 1981/1982-1982/1983 1986 (Box 2)
- Building and Grounds Committee-Correspondence 1981 (Box 2)
- Finance Committee-Correspondence (2 folders) 1980-1981 (Box 2)